Princess Mystery Dungeon
A Ludum Dare 20 entry by Adam Gardner (philomory)

Theme: It's Dangerous to go Alone! Take This!

Princess Mystery Dungeon combines zelda-esque gameplay with roguelike procedurally generated dungeons.  
The goal is simple: explore the dungeon, get through the Magic Door and enter the portal beyond it to fight the terrifying boss!

== Controls ==
 Arrow keys move, Z attacks with your sword, X uses your wall-breaking secondary item, if you've acquired it. During a text-message, press enter or return to clear the message and get on with things.

== Dungeon Guide ==

Collect keys to open locked doors (the ones with keyholes in them).
Hit switches (diamonds things) to open sealed doors (the plain ones).
Collect the Magic Key to open the Magic Door (crazy door with runes and such).

Collect hearts to restore your health.

== Hints ==

Sometimes you have to kill all the enemies in a room to find a key.

When you hit a switch, it opens a sealed door somewhere else in the dungeon. Return to places you've already visited; a new path may have opened up!

You can find hearts by killing enemies.
